really-simple-ssl.com 2017-03-21

# Privacy Statement - Really Simple SSL

### Information collection

As a company, we respect the privacy of our users. Any personal information we receive through our products will be handled trustfully with great care and responsibility.

We will only ask for personal information if you want to contact us and/or if you want to buy the premium version. In that case we will ask for your name, email and address. This data is needed to process the payment.

To handle the licensing of a premium plugin we will also register your ip-address and domain on which the plugin is downloaded and used.

### Purpose of dataprocessing

Any personal information you submit will be used for the direct purpose of the following things:

  * Process the order of a bought version of the software.
  * Process customer service (including question and complaints).
  * Handle licensing.

We will never sell your personal data or provide your personal data to third parties unless required by law.

It is not allowed to provide data concerning children below thirteen. If we notice such information in our systems, we will delete this data as soon as possible.

### Right to inspect and correct personal information

We are doing our best to register your details correctly. Under circumstances caused by technical and/or other difficulties it may occur that the details are inaccurate.

As a customer you have the right to know which details are processed, and you have the right to have us adjust and/or remove these details. If this is the case, please contact us.

### Adjustments to this privacy statement.

In case of changes to this statement, the changes will be published on really-simple-ssl.com.
